Cayden Dunn

Arlington, VA

Email: Caydendunn2121@gmail.com

Phone: 860-412-4687

SUMMARY

As a versatile machine learning engineer and computer scientist, I specialize in SKlearn, Apache Spark, Databricks, Azure, SQL, and Python. My focus is on process automation, discerning novel problem spaces, and emphasizing not every problem needs a machine learning solution.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Machine Learning Engineer @ ClearForce | Vienna VA | Dec 2021 - Current 2024

- Developed model to win 300,000\$ contract and partnership with Virginia VA to prevent veteran suicide using SKlearn, DataBricks, Apache Spark, MLFlow, and SQL
- Automated data processing to create visualizations for business teams using Python and PowerBI

Computer scientist @ Medical University of SC, Mulholland Neuroscience Lab

Charleston SC | Nov 2020 - Nov 2021

- Integrated behavioral analysis into brainwave analysis studies using Raspberry Pi and OpenCV
- Assisted in creating 3D brain renderings with varying protein stains using Imaris
- Processed data collected from nodes in mouse brains using KiloSort and MATLAB

Frontend Developer (Internship) @ Ability Beyond | Remote, Danbury Ct | May 2020 - Aug 2020

Automated shift scheduling for non-profit, reducing required shift managers, by creating a web app using Flutter.

College Tutor @ College of Charleston | Charleston SC | Aug 2019 - May 2022

• Tutored other college age students in Math and Computer Science topics.

PUBLICATIONS

- Dunn, C., Navid, H., (2023). "Gestalt: Combining GPT Language Models and Computational Knowledge Engines."
 URI: https://hdl.handle.net/10125/107007 PDF
- Dunn, C., Kris, G., (2023). "BicePy: Bilingual Description of Compiler Errors in Python." DOI: 10.1109/VL-HCC57772.2023.00038 PDF
- Dunn, C.,Kris G., (2023) "Fingerprinting of Malware Families Under Uncertainty." IFIP PDF

EDUCATION

College of Charleston | Master of Science in Data Science and Analytics | Aug 22' to June 23'

- GPA 4/4
- 1st place College of Charleston Graduate Poster Session

College of Charleston | Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Aug 18' to Aug 22'

- GPA 3.78/4
- Honors: Magna Cum Laude, Achieved President's list 5 semesters, Achieved Dean's list 3 semesters
- Relevant Activities: Cyber security club member, Women in STEM club member, Club Lacrosse Captain

Stanford Online | Machine Learning Certificate | Dec 20' to Aug 20'

Coursera Course taught by Andrew Ng that builds foundational concepts of Machine learning models.

VOLUNTEER

REACH | mentor | Sandy Hook, CT | Sep 2015 - June 2018

• Provided one-to-one social and academic support to mentees (at-risk youth)

Ben's Lighthouse | Volunteer/Representative | Sandy Hook, CT | July 2014 - June 2018

 Crew team member in Greely, Colorado. Repaired homes damaged by flooding. Met and shared experiences with the survivors of the Columbine School shooting.

INTERESTS

Video games, AI, Longevity, Lacrosse, Hiking, Climbing, Automation, Building PC's, Keyboards